<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<home>
	<summary>
		<price>$1,295,000</price>
		<bd>4</bd>
		<ba>4</ba>
		<area>4,691</area>
	</summary>
	<address>
		<street_address>2225 Warbler Way,</street_address>
		<city_state> Austin, TX 78735</city_state>
	</address>
	<overview>Beautiful home in the sought-after community of Wimberly Lane in Barton Creek, with close proximity to private schools, the Omni Barton Creek Resort and Spa, &amp; several acclaimed Barton Creek golf courses. The greenbelt corner lot contains a trail leading directly from the back yard down to Barton Creek. The grand yet comforting home introduces a sprawling main living space that accommodates multiple family needs, furniture arrangements and entertainment plans. The expansive, interconnected space, plentiful natural light, and luxuriously subdued accents with gas fireplace, wood floors, and high ceilings throughout instills peace and tranquility. Plantation shutters allow for privacy and light control throughout the home and a full range of windows open to the deck and private back yard. Let the outdoors in with easy viewing of a private back lawn. Enjoy a plethora of living options in massive rooms equipped with plentiful closets and windows. A private guest or 'In-Law' suite on the first floor is conveniently situated with a separate exterior entrance. An office with French doors makes working from home an event separate from the main living space. Find two extra-large living areas with vaulted ceilings upstairs that can function as play spaces, media rooms, or a 5th bedroom. The Master Suite contains coffered ceilings, a spacious garden tub and shower, a large Master closet and a gorgeous array of shuttered windows that allows for both seclusion and tranquility. With useful appliance selections, extra-wide Sub-zero fridge space, rustic cabinetry, granite counters and a sweepingly large kitchen area, both family and guests have plenty of room to work and play in this home. 2225 Warbler Way's unique connectedness with nature and seclusion in the heart of Barton Creek is also found in the well-planned yard and front patio, which is perfect for a quiet evening of relaxation and entertainment. With private schools only minutes away, easy access to the shops and businesses of Bee Cave, Southwest Austin and Westlake, and a short drive into Central Austin and Lakeway, 2225 Warbler Way is truly a gem for any buyer.Read more</overview>
	<listing_agent>
		<agentName>Beth Drewett</agentName>
		<phoneNumber>512-575-3644</phoneNumber>
		<agentLicenseNumber/>
		<postingGroupName>Compass RE Texas, LLC</postingGroupName>
		<postingWebsiteLinkText>Compass RE Texas, LLC</postingWebsiteLinkText>
	</listing_agent>
	<facts>
		<key name="Type:">Single Family</key>
		<key name="Year built:">2001</key>
		<key name="Heating:">Forced air</key>
		<key name="Cooling:">Central</key>
		<key name="Parking:">2 spaces</key>
		<key name="HOA:">$108/month</key>
		<key name="Lot:">0.4 acres</key>
		<key name="Price/sqft:">$276</key>
	</facts>
	<interior_details>
		<item>
			<item>Bedrooms and bathrooms</item>
			<item>
				<item>Bedrooms: 4</item>
				<item>Bathrooms: 4</item>
				<item>Full bathrooms: 4</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Flooring</item>
			<item>
				<item>Flooring: Carpet, Hardwood, Tile</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Heating</item>
			<item>
				<item>Heating features: Electric, Gas, Forced air</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Cooling</item>
			<item>
				<item>Cooling features: Central</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Appliances</item>
			<item>
				<item>Appliances included: Dishwasher, Microwave</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Other interior features</item>
			<item>
				<item>Total interior livable area: 4,691 sqft</item>
				<item>Total number of fireplaces: 1</item>
				<item>Virtual tour: View virtual tour</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</interior_details>
	<property_details>
		<item>
			<item>Parking</item>
			<item>
				<item>Parking features: Attached Garage</item>
				<item>Garage spaces: 2</item>
				<item>Attached garage: Yes</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Property</item>
			<item>
				<item>Stories: 2</item>
				<item>Entry location: 1st Floor Entry</item>
				<item>Spa included: Yes</item>
				<item>Exterior features: Stone</item>
				<item>Patio and porch details: Patio, Covered</item>
				<item>Residential vegetation: Trees-Medium (20 Ft - 40 Ft)</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Lot</item>
			<item>
				<item>Lot size: 0.4 acres</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Other property information</item>
			<item>
				<item>Parcel number: 01153801180000</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</property_details>
	<construction_details>
		<item>
			<item>Type and style</item>
			<item>
				<item>Home type: Single Family</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Material information</item>
			<item>
				<item>Foundation: Slab</item>
				<item>Roof: Composition</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Condition</item>
			<item>
				<item>New construction: No</item>
				<item>Year built: 2001</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</construction_details>
	<utility_and_energy_details>
		<item>
			<item>Utility</item>
			<item>
				<item>Electric utility on property: Yes</item>
				<item>Utilities for property: Electricity Available, Natural Gas Available</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Green energy</item>
			<item>
				<item>Sunscore: Great solar potentialSun Number™: 78.39</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</utility_and_energy_details>
	<community_and_neibhourhood_details>
		<item>
			<item>Community</item>
			<item>
				<item>Community features: Gated</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Location</item>
			<item>
				<item>Region: Austin</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</community_and_neibhourhood_details>
</home>
