<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<home>
	<summary>
		<price>$674,900</price>
		<bd>4</bd>
		<ba>4</ba>
		<area>1,480</area>
	</summary>
	<address>
		<street_address>812 S Oakley Blvd,</street_address>
		<city_state> Chicago, IL 60612</city_state>
	</address>
	<overview>Rare Landmark District offering by Vari Architects, exceptional newly rehabbed historic row home in the heart of the Tri-Taylor/Medical District neighborhood is a must see! It is a brick Victorian row home with all the modern finishes of new construction without losing any of the original historic charm the neighborhood is known to have. Built in the 1880s this row home is a legal 2 flat comprised of a 3 bed/2.5 bath duplex-up owner's unit and a generous 1 bed/1 bath garden rental unit. The owner's unit features soaring ceiling heights, exposed brick in the large living room, a fireplace, beautiful hardwood floors throughout, large front bay windows looking over the quiet tree lined street and ample closet space, in-unit washer and dryer and the original arched entry door and window details. The modern kitchen has ample quartz countertop space, shaker cabinets offering abundant storage, stainless steel Whirlpool appliances, and a large island with bar seating. The kitchen leads into a light filled and expansive sunroom/mudroom, rear deck and then out into the private garden. The back garden is a beautiful, low maintenance space with a large tree, flower bed, artificial turf and pavers for relaxing and entertaining with friends and family. The baths are bright and modern, offering a large walk in shower, soaker tub, quartz counters and beautiful tile. The garden unit's style and high-end finishes reflect that of the owner's unit. Modern kitchen with flat panel cabinets, quartz counter tops, Whirlpool appliances, large living room space with a fireplace, wood grain flooring throughout, in-unit laundry, mud room and separate mechanicals. The rental unit has great rental income potential, but can also be used as an in-law suite for family, housing for nanny/care givers, private quarantine office space, or as an Airbnb. So many great options! The home includes two parking spots for everyone's parking needs. This home is just steps to the Blue Line and CTA stop, quick access to I-290 to get downtown or the western suburbs, walking distance of the Medical District, excellent dining and shopping, public parks and so much more! Everything inside and out shows quality workmanship and the love of historic details combined with all the modern comforts. Sale includes HWA 1-year home warranty.Read more</overview>
	<listing_agent>
		<agentName>Karen Biazar</agentName>
		<phoneNumber>773-252-0600</phoneNumber>
		<agentLicenseNumber/>
		<postingGroupName>North Clybourn Group  Inc.</postingGroupName>
		<postingWebsiteLinkText>North Clybourn Group  Inc.</postingWebsiteLinkText>
	</listing_agent>
	<facts>
		<key name="Type:">Multiple Occupancy</key>
		<key name="Year built:">1880</key>
		<key name="Heating:">Forced air, Gas</key>
		<key name="Cooling:">Central</key>
		<key name="Parking:">1 space</key>
		<key name="Price/sqft:">$456</key>
	</facts>
	<interior_details>
		<item>
			<item>Bedrooms and bathrooms</item>
			<item>
				<item>Bedrooms: 4</item>
				<item>Bathrooms: 4</item>
				<item>Full bathrooms: 3</item>
				<item>1/2 bathrooms: 1</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Flooring</item>
			<item>
				<item>Flooring: Carpet, Hardwood</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Heating</item>
			<item>
				<item>Heating features: Forced air, Gas</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Cooling</item>
			<item>
				<item>Cooling features: Central</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Appliances</item>
			<item>
				<item>Appliances included: Dishwasher, Dryer, Microwave, Refrigerator, Washer</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Other interior features</item>
			<item>
				<item>Total interior livable area: 1,480 sqft</item>
				<item>Virtual tour: View virtual tour</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</interior_details>
	<property_details>
		<item>
			<item>Parking</item>
			<item>
				<item>Total spaces: 1</item>
				<item>Parking features: Garage - Detached, Covered</item>
				<item>Garage spaces: 1</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Property</item>
			<item>
				<item>Exterior features: Brick</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Lot</item>
			<item>
				<item>Lot size: 2,077 sqft</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Other property information</item>
			<item>
				<item>Parcel number: 1718315036</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</property_details>
	<construction_details>
		<item>
			<item>Type and style</item>
			<item>
				<item>Home type: Multiple Occupancy</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Material information</item>
			<item>
				<item>Construction materials: masonry</item>
				<item>Roof: Built-up</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Condition</item>
			<item>
				<item>New construction: No</item>
				<item>Year built: 1880</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</construction_details>
	<utility_and_energy_details>
		<item>
			<item>Utility</item>
			<item>
				<item>Sewer information: Sewer-Public</item>
			</item>
		</item>
		<item>
			<item>Green energy</item>
			<item>
				<item>Sunscore: Great solar potentialSun Number™: 83.77</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</utility_and_energy_details>
	<community_and_neibhourhood_details>
		<item>
			<item>Location</item>
			<item>
				<item>Region: Chicago</item>
			</item>
		</item>
	</community_and_neibhourhood_details>
</home>
